All right, you're done. Let's go look at the
solution. Where we left off last time as you can
see we have two empty queries for LOCATION_ID and
LOCATION. These two queries look a lot like the queries
we have for weather. For LOCATION_ID this looks almost
exactly like what we do for weather. Except we use
a hard coded query, rather than relying on the one
passed into the function. Since we know that this is
always going to be a long integer value, it is
easy to just build the value into the query string. Location,
on the other hand, looks almost exactly like the weather
query. We just pass all the parameters into the database. You
didn't think you're going to get away without testing, did you?
Don't worry, it's really easy to add this test. It turns
out that calling our function within the provider, works almost
exactly the same as the way we did the weather table.
All we have to do is replace WeatherEntry.CONTENT_URI with
LocationEntry.CONTENT_URI. And of course we still have to delete the
two columns that we can't support. Now that will actually
work. So, let's test that to make sure that works.
And our test passed, as expected. The interesting thing about
this test is that it's just only testing the first
query and it just happens to work because we deleted
the database before the start. It'd be much more interesting
to query for the row that we just inserted. And this will test the
other query. Now, let's run the test again. And those also passed. So, we have
some of our queries from our content
provider functioning. But, unfortunately, we still have
to do some of the more complicated
things in the provider. Let's talk about joins.